Hula, Erich; Papers ger044
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Pamphlets, 8; 378 file folders
  - UNESCO.Round the World with a Postage Stamp. A Booklet for Teachers and Students about the Universal Postal Union, 1954 April (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 102)
  - UNESCO.Some Suggestions on Teaching about Collective Security, 1952 (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 103)
  - United Nations Association of the United States of America.Controlling Conflicts in the 1970s, 1969 April (Box 26 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 104)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems.Problem I: Should the Governments of the United Nations at this Time Formulate and Announce a "Common Strategy for Peace"?, ca. 1943 (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 1)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems.Problem II: By What Method and Through What Stages Should the Final Peace Settlement be Reached?, 1943 (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 2)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems.Problem III: Treatment of Defeated Enemy Countries. Germany, 1943 March 03 (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 3)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems.Summary of Repliles on Problem III. Treatment of Defeated Enemy Countries. Germany, 1943 September 30 (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 4)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems.Problem IV: Should There Be an International Organization for General Security Against Military Aggression, and Should the United States Participate in Such an Organization?, 1943 April 09 (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 5)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems.Problem IV: Should There Be an International Organization for General Security Against Military Aggression, and Should the United States Participate in Such an Organization? Analysis, Part II, 1943 (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 6)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems.Problem V: Relief and Rehabilitation. Analysis, 1943 (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 7)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems.Problem VI: International Economic Collaboration. Analysis, 1943 July 01 (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 8)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems.Problem VII: Education and World Peace, 1943 August (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 9)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems.Problem VIII: Proposed Methods and Agencies for International Economic Collaboration. Should America Participate in Them?, 1943 September 01 (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 10)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems.Problem IX: Colonies and Dependent Areas, 1943 (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 11)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems.Problem X: The Protection By International Action of the Freedom of the Individual Within the State, 1943 (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 12)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems.Problem XI: Post-War Treatment of Japan, 1944 January (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 13)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems.Problem XII: China in the Post-War World, 1944 February (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 14)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems.Problem XIII: International Air Traffic After the War, 1944 March (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 15)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems.Problem XIV: Post-War Relations with the Soviet Union, 1944 April (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 16)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems.Problem XV: Post-War Relations with the British Commonwealth of Nations, 1944 May (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 17)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems.Problem XVI: American Membership in a General International Organization: Constitutional Difficulties, 1944 July (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 18)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems.Problem XVII: Peaceful Settlement of International Disputes, 1944 September (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 19)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems.Problem XVIII: The Dumbarton Oaks Proposals: The Enforcement of Peace, 1944 December (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 20)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems.Problem XIX: The Dumbarton Oaks Proposals: Economic and Social Cooperation, 1945 February (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 21)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems.Problem XX: Problems of United States Participation in the United Nations Organization, 1945 May (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 22)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems.Final Report on the Work of the Committee, 1942-1945, 1945 October (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 23)
  - Vambery, Rustem.The Hungarian Problem, Undated (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 24)
  - Van Wagenen, Richard W.Research in the International Organization Field. Some Notes on a Possible Focus, 1952 (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 25)
  - Vinacke, Harold M.United States Policy Toward China, 1961 (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 26)
  - Vyshinsky, A. Y.The Soviet Position on Prohibition of Atomic Weapons and International Control of Atomic Energy, 1949 November (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 27)
  - Vyshinsky, A. Y.Speeches by A. Y. Vyshinsky on Measures Against the Threat of Another War and for Strengthening Peace and Friendship Among Nations, 1951 December (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 28)
  - Waldheim, Kurt.Introduction to the Report of the Secretary-General on the Work of the Organization, 1973 August (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 29)
  - The Washington Center of Foreign Policy Research.Two Communist Manifestoes, 1961 (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 30)
  - Weiler, Lawrence D.The Arms Race, Secret Negotiations and the Congress, 1976 (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 31)
  - Wilcox, Francis O.UN and the Nonaligned Nations, 1962 September 20 (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 32)
  - The Woodrow Wilson Foundation.Proposals for the Establishment of a General International Organization as submitted by The Dumbarton Oaks Conference, 1944 October 09 (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 33)
  - Woodward, E. L.Some Political Consequences of the Atomic Bomb, 1946 (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 34)
  - World Peace Foundation.The United Nations in the Making: Basic Documents, 1945 (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 35)
  - Wriggins, Howard and Edwin A. Bock.The Status of the United Nations Secretariat. Role of the Administrative Tribunal, 1954 September (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 36)
  - Wright, Quincy.Human Rights and World Order, ca. 1943 (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 37)
  - Zhdanov, A. A.Organizational Problems of the Communist Party, 1937 February (Box 27 (8-Pamphlets), Folder 38)